# **Fuchs** Maxime

COMPUTER SCIENCE ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

# CONTACT



514-418-5904



Montreal



maxime.fuchs1@gmail.com

#### FOREIGN LANGUAGES

FRENCH - mother tongue

ENGLISH - advanced

DUTCH - intermediate

GERMAN - intermediate

SPANISH - beginner

## EXPERIENCE

## MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER | Solid State of Mind

Montreal, Canada | October 2021 - April 2023

Reinforement Learning | Environments implemented in Unity Research and implementation of ML papers Python and C++ implementation on real robot using ROS

### ANALYST PROGRAMMER | IMDS

Montreal, Canada | May 2021 - August 2021

Document classification based on image recognition (OCR) C++ Sofware developping

Research in team with PhD researchers

#### WEB DEVELOPPER | SkillX | Internship

Lille, France | Summer 2020

Web development

Cloud experience | AWS formation and certificate

## JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPPER | Anamnesia | Internship

Strasbourg, France | Summer 2019

Developping multimedia desktop apps using Electron.js Reproduction of templates made by Graphic Designers and adding animations.

#### ENTREPRENEUR

France | 2019 - 2020

Web Development, Front-End and Back-End

### EDUCATION

## Masters Science | Ecole Polytechnique de Montreal

Montreal, Canada - Double Diploma | August 2019 - August 2021 Major: Computer Science | Minor: Artificial Intelligence Additional Courses: Data Viz, Video Games Conception

## Engineer Diploma | Mines de Douai

Douai, France - Double Diploma | September 2017 - August 2021 Major: Information Technology | Minor: Android development Additional Courses: Network infrastructure, Database, Project Managment

#### ABOUT ME

## Preparation Classes for Engineering Schools

Strasbourg, France | September 2015 - July 2017

Advanced Mathematics and Physics

#### French former basketball student athlete, I studied and worked in AI/ML in Canada for four years. Really curious about new technologies, I am looking for a new challenge where I could continue learning about a forever evolving

# SKILLS

# MACHINE LEARNING, DATA

Math: Statistics, Bayesian Theory

ML: Keras, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Scikit-Learn Data: Numpy, Pandas, d3.js, Plotly

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

WFB

ANDROID

GAMING

OTHER

C++ | VISUAL STUDIO

HTML | CSS | JS | PHP | SQL

JAVA | KOTLIN | ANDROID STUDIO

C# | C++ | UNITY | UNREAL ENGINE

JAVA | PHARO | SOLIDITY

CLOUD

AWS - Certified Cloud Partitioner







field.





